<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on </title>
    <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 04:22:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://iamb4uc.xyz/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GRUB - *Literally for coomies*</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/grub-literally-for-coomies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 04:22:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/grub-literally-for-coomies/</guid>
      <description>Here is a quick conversation between me and my friend about grub
&amp;gt; [Friend]: Hey I got this new refurbished thinkpad x230, what do you think? [[image attachment]] &amp;gt; [Me]: Looks pretty good. Time to install some obscure operating system into it. &amp;gt; [Friend]: Yeah :skull-emoji: &amp;gt; [Me]: Let me see how you set this up after you are done with all the installation and shit. &amp;gt; [Friend]: ok &amp;gt; [Friend]: [[image attachment]] &amp;gt; [Me]: Looks neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of AI in Education Sector</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/impact-of-ai-in-education-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 22:38:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/impact-of-ai-in-education-sector/</guid>
      <description>The use of AI technology in education is rapidly growing, and chatbots like ChatGPT are becoming increasingly popular as tools to assist students with their homework and assignments. However, this trend has not been without controversy. Recently, it was reported that the state of New York has banned the use of chatbots like ChatGPT in schools, due to concerns about their potential misuse by students.
The decision to ban chatbots in New York schools was made after it was reported that some students were using these tools to cheat on their homework and assignments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets Join Tilde Varsh</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:48:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks ago I came across this thing called a tilde on the gnulinuxindia.org website, while lurking around the web. I had zero idea about what it was about or what even is it. So in their terms it is
An India-based shared unix system which focuses on mutual development of skills and sharing of ideas. Services are secondary in this tilde, community is prime.
&amp;ndash; Tildevarsh
Still confused watch this Video</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
