<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on </title>
    <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:34:57 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://iamb4uc.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AI This AI That</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/ai-this-ai-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 09:34:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/ai-this-ai-that/</guid>
      <description>AI is making you dumb. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Social Media</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/onsocialmedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:25:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/onsocialmedia/</guid>
      <description>Last day I got this email and here what it reads:
Hey there, I had this question for you and wanted to know about your thoughts/insight on this topic and would appreciate your insights on the following points:
Positive aspects: What do you consider the main benefits of social media? Any specific instances where it has played a constructive role in your life or someone you know?
Challenges: From your observations, what are the major drawbacks or negative effects of social media?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Mode</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/ghost-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:24:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/ghost-mode/</guid>
      <description>Ghost mode is the act of going complete offline and returning as the best version of yourself. It does not mean that you need to be rude or tell everyone to follow what you are doing.
Here is the complete guide of how to get your life together and GRIND MOTHERFUCKER.
Delete everything that keeps you on your phone:
Limit the time you spend on social media each day, or better yet don&amp;rsquo;t use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRUB - *Literally for coomies*</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/grub-literally-for-coomies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 04:22:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/grub-literally-for-coomies/</guid>
      <description>Here is a quick conversation between me and my friend about grub
&amp;gt; [Friend]: Hey I got this new refurbished thinkpad x230, what do you think? [[image attachment]] &amp;gt; [Me]: Looks pretty good. Time to install some obscure operating system into it. &amp;gt; [Friend]: Yeah :skull-emoji: &amp;gt; [Me]: Let me see how you set this up after you are done with all the installation and shit. &amp;gt; [Friend]: ok &amp;gt; [Friend]: [[image attachment]] &amp;gt; [Me]: Looks neat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of AI in Education Sector</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/impact-of-ai-in-education-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 22:38:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/impact-of-ai-in-education-sector/</guid>
      <description>The use of AI technology in education is rapidly growing, and chatbots like ChatGPT are becoming increasingly popular as tools to assist students with their homework and assignments. However, this trend has not been without controversy. Recently, it was reported that the state of New York has banned the use of chatbots like ChatGPT in schools, due to concerns about their potential misuse by students.
The decision to ban chatbots in New York schools was made after it was reported that some students were using these tools to cheat on their homework and assignments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stoicism</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 12:46:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/stoicism/</guid>
      <description>Stoicism has been a guiding principle in my life for the past few years. It has helped me to navigate through difficult times and find inner peace and fulfillment. The concept of &amp;ldquo;ataraxia&amp;rdquo; or inner peace, has been particularly valuable to me. Accepting that some things are beyond our control and focusing on the things that are within our control has allowed me to let go of my attachment to certain outcomes and find peace in the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Torrent</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/make-your-own-torrent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 10:13:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/make-your-own-torrent/</guid>
      <description>You are based if you seed torrent.
&amp;ndash;Probably Someone
Torrent have a bad image when it comes to downloading thing, like movies, music and most importently ISO&amp;rsquo;s for your Linux distro.
Well, then lets not waist time and make and make some torrents.
Pre-requisites Qbittorrent(client) A good/reliable/fast internet connection The file you want to seed Well if you have all the above then follow the steps below.
If not then Fuck off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets Join Tilde Varsh</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:48:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks ago I came across this thing called a tilde on the gnulinuxindia.org website, while lurking around the web. I had zero idea about what it was about or what even is it. So in their terms it is
An India-based shared unix system which focuses on mutual development of skills and sharing of ideas. Services are secondary in this tilde, community is prime.
&amp;ndash; Tildevarsh
Still confused watch this Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neovim Customization</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/nvim-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 08:48:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/nvim-customization/</guid>
      <description>Why use vim and neovim over other text editors and IDEs? For me, I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved minimalism and performance over ease of use and other flashy bloat no one really uses and cares about. This why I personally use Terminal-based text editors. Preferably VIM or Neovim. Tho I currently, am running Neovim, but both of them are basically the same. NeoVIM is a little bit more extensible than VIM and easy to manage imo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a wanna-be systems-level engineer with a passion for UNIX-like operating systems as well as other Free-and-Open-source software and a knack for hardware tinkering. I love digging into low-level details to understand how things really work, and using that knowledge to build robust, reliable software. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s optimizing performance, improving security, or just exploring new possibilities, I&amp;rsquo;m always looking for ways to push the boundaries of what&amp;rsquo;s possible with code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/anime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/anime/</guid>
      <description>Neon-Genesis Evangalion
One of my most favorite anime of all time, it was one of the first anime that made me interested in serious topics such as mental health, trauma in an ANIME. It is very rare to see good quality anime these days. But if you are a sucker for good plot and short anime that wont take too much dedication to watch through like me you will love this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/book/</guid>
      <description>The C Programming Language [Brian W. Kernighan | Dennis M. Ritche]
The Linux Command Line [William Shotts]
Design of the UNIX Operating System [Maurice Bach]
Designing BSD Rootkits [Joseph Kong]
The Manga Guide to Databases [Shoko Azuma]
Thus spoke Zarathustra [Friedrich Nietzsche]
Beyond Good and Evil [Friedrich Nietzsche]
Meditation [Marcus Aurelius]
12 Rules For Life [Jordan B. Peterson]
Atomic Habits [James Clear]
Maps of meaning [Jordan B. Peterson]
48 Laws Of Power [Greene, Robert]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/donate/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for dropping by here are few ways you can help me fund this project and all the development of my free and open source software. You can either send me crypto via the following wallet addresses or send me using paypal.
Monero: 47kE91oAWUsC7dX2wpP2MhdV5WRA3iv3YgptaTTxXdeqF7j9XaYQUgzbk12Xb4Yf8RJxgDLEUuEEidV6Ev9uGW5VVTDJs91 Ethereum: 0x2F78287646Acd6e3D40cCb6403C7d2b4b663dE48 Kofi: https://www.buymeacoffee.com/b4uc </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/projects/</guid>
      <description>Dotfiles These dotfiles are very crucial to my development process and are a bonus for anyone who like to use vim/neovim and some other terminal applications. If you want to see for you yourself head over to the repo and clone it. Also feel free to improve the existing or creating new solutions to problems in that repo.
No-More-Style-Please A Hugo theme that is made to look super minimal, yet modern.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
