<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Everything about me in one place on b4uc&#39;s dingus blogs</title>
    <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Everything about me in one place on b4uc&#39;s dingus blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 21:30:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://iamb4uc.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>usefull resources</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/usefullrec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 20:57:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/usefullrec/</guid>
      <description>here are some usefull resources I rely on suckless.org cat-v landchad.net based.cooking eff fsf ~varsh you can use all of these by bookmarking them in your browser and donating to these services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thoughts on modern medicine</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/thoughts-on-modern-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:04:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/thoughts-on-modern-medicine/</guid>
      <description>HOMEOPATHY: turning water into money since 1810
&amp;ndash;Dr Aust
Tl;Dr
Its not just black and white, good or bad. I have mixed feeling but i am optimistic about this.
TOC The bad part The good part The bad part It not that medicine is evil, we all need them to live a healthy and less stressful life. Its the medicine companies or as every social media influencer puts it &amp;ldquo;BIG PHARMA&amp;rdquo; I hate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>neovim customization</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/nvim-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 08:48:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/nvim-customization/</guid>
      <description>Why use vim and neovim over other text editors and IDEs? For me, I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved minimalism and performance over ease of use and other flashy bloat no one really uses and cares about. This why I personally use Terminal-based text editors. Preferably VIM or Neovim. Tho I currently, am running Neovim, but both of them are basically the same. NeoVIM is a little bit more extensible than VIM and easy to manage imo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/book/</guid>
      <description>Here I will be posting some of my recommendations for the books I read. Tho these may not be all computer or tech related but would probaly be a good read if you want to read something new.
Also if you want to purchase these books please do so from the provided link as it is an affiliate like which would give me a small commision on your purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
