<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on 🏠 Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on 🏠 Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 20:29:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Make a Local Email Spam Filter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/make-a-local-email-spam-filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 20:29:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/make-a-local-email-spam-filter/</guid>
      <description>In this we will be creating a spam filter using a Raspberry Pi to remove all the incoming spam messages.&#xA;This assumes that you already have a fully working Raspberry Pi with any of the Linux distros available with Systemd as an init service. Note:&#xA;This only works for unmonitored clients such as thunderbird and other offline FOSS applications. I have not tried it on online email clients like Gmail and other proprietary spying websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse-Engineering Private APIs with MITM Proxy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/how-to-reverse-engineer-a-private-api-with-mitm-proxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 22:49:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/how-to-reverse-engineer-a-private-api-with-mitm-proxy/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This is for educational purposes, do not abuse this method. Developers can often struggle to find the data they need for their personal projects due to certain services locking down their API’s.&#xA;So I wanted to show you a way you can get the data you need.&#xA;What is MITM Proxy and how does it work? MITM stands for Man-in-the-Middle and mitmproxy is exactly that. It allows you to send data through a proxy that acts as a man-in-the-middle so you can read the request and responses being sent to and from the server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup QEMU and KVM in Void Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/setup-qemu-and-kvm-in-void-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:38:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/setup-qemu-and-kvm-in-void-linux/</guid>
      <description>Here are the steps on how to set this up:&#xA;First, become superuser su Update xbps-install -Suy Now install all the required packages xbps-install dbus qemu libvirtd virt-manager bridge-utils iptables2 Now link and enable the services ln -sf /etc/sv/dbus/ /var/service/ ln -sf /etc/sv/libvirtd/ /var/service/ ln -sf /etc/sv/virtlockd/ /var/service/ ln -sf /etc/sv/virtlogd/ /var/service/ Done, Reboot </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Social Media</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/onsocialmedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:25:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/onsocialmedia/</guid>
      <description>Last day I got this email and here what it reads:&#xA;Hey there, I had this question for you and wanted to know about your thoughts/insight on this topic and would appreciate your insights on the following points:&#xA;Positive aspects: What do you consider the main benefits of social media? Any specific instances where it has played a constructive role in your life or someone you know?&#xA;Challenges: From your observations, what are the major drawbacks or negative effects of social media?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Mode</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ghost-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:24:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ghost-mode/</guid>
      <description>Ghost mode is the act of going complete offline and returning as the best version of yourself. It does not mean that you need to be rude or tell everyone to follow what you are doing.&#xA;Here is the complete guide of how to get your life together and GRIND MOTHERFUCKER.&#xA;Delete everything that keeps you on your phone:&#xA;Limit the time you spend on social media each day, or better yet don&amp;rsquo;t use them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRUB - *Literally for coomies*</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/grub-literally-for-coomies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 04:22:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/grub-literally-for-coomies/</guid>
      <description>Here is a quick conversation between me and my friend about grub&#xA;&amp;gt; [Friend]: Hey I got this new refurbished thinkpad x230, what do you think? [[image attachment]] &amp;gt; [Me]: Looks pretty good. Time to install some obscure operating system into it. &amp;gt; [Friend]: Yeah :skull-emoji: &amp;gt; [Me]: Let me see how you set this up after you are done with all the installation and shit. &amp;gt; [Friend]: ok &amp;gt; [Friend]: [[image attachment]] &amp;gt; [Me]: Looks neat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of AI in Education Sector</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/impact-of-ai-in-education-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 22:38:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/impact-of-ai-in-education-sector/</guid>
      <description>The use of AI technology in education is rapidly growing, and chatbots like ChatGPT are becoming increasingly popular as tools to assist students with their homework and assignments. However, this trend has not been without controversy. Recently, it was reported that the state of New York has banned the use of chatbots like ChatGPT in schools, due to concerns about their potential misuse by students.&#xA;The decision to ban chatbots in New York schools was made after it was reported that some students were using these tools to cheat on their homework and assignments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stoicism</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 12:46:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/stoicism/</guid>
      <description>Stoicism has been a guiding principle in my life for the past few years. It has helped me to navigate through difficult times and find inner peace and fulfillment. The concept of &amp;ldquo;ataraxia&amp;rdquo; or inner peace, has been particularly valuable to me. Accepting that some things are beyond our control and focusing on the things that are within our control has allowed me to let go of my attachment to certain outcomes and find peace in the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Torrent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/make-your-own-torrent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 10:13:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/make-your-own-torrent/</guid>
      <description>You are based if you seed torrent.&#xA;&amp;ndash;Probably Someone&#xA;Torrent have a bad image when it comes to downloading thing, like movies, music and most importently ISO&amp;rsquo;s for your Linux distro.&#xA;Well, then lets not waist time and make and make some torrents.&#xA;Pre-requisites Qbittorrent(client) A good/reliable/fast internet connection The file you want to seed Well if you have all the above then follow the steps below.&#xA;If not then Fuck off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lets Join Tilde Varsh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:48:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks ago I came across this thing called a tilde on the gnulinuxindia.org website, while lurking around the web. I had zero idea about what it was about or what even is it. So in their terms it is&#xA;An India-based shared unix system which focuses on mutual development of skills and sharing of ideas. Services are secondary in this tilde, community is prime.&#xA;&amp;ndash; Tildevarsh&#xA;Still confused watch this Video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neovim Customization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/nvim-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 08:48:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/nvim-customization/</guid>
      <description>Why use vim and neovim over other text editors and IDEs? For me, I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved minimalism and performance over ease of use and other flashy bloat no one really uses and cares about. This why I personally use Terminal-based text editors. Preferably VIM or Neovim. Tho I currently, am running Neovim, but both of them are basically the same. NeoVIM is a little bit more extensible than VIM and easy to manage imo.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
