<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>selfImprovement on </title>
    <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/tags/selfimprovement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in selfImprovement on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:25:15 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://iamb4uc.xyz/tags/selfimprovement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On Social Media</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/onsocialmedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 20:25:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/onsocialmedia/</guid>
      <description>Last day I got this email and here what it reads:
Hey there, I had this question for you and wanted to know about your thoughts/insight on this topic and would appreciate your insights on the following points:
Positive aspects: What do you consider the main benefits of social media? Any specific instances where it has played a constructive role in your life or someone you know?
Challenges: From your observations, what are the major drawbacks or negative effects of social media?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghost Mode</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/ghost-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:24:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/ghost-mode/</guid>
      <description>Ghost mode is the act of going complete offline and returning as the best version of yourself. It does not mean that you need to be rude or tell everyone to follow what you are doing.
Here is the complete guide of how to get your life together and GRIND MOTHERFUCKER.
Delete everything that keeps you on your phone:
Limit the time you spend on social media each day, or better yet don&amp;rsquo;t use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stoicism</title>
      <link>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/stoicism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 12:46:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iamb4uc.xyz/post/stoicism/</guid>
      <description>Stoicism has been a guiding principle in my life for the past few years. It has helped me to navigate through difficult times and find inner peace and fulfillment. The concept of &amp;ldquo;ataraxia&amp;rdquo; or inner peace, has been particularly valuable to me. Accepting that some things are beyond our control and focusing on the things that are within our control has allowed me to let go of my attachment to certain outcomes and find peace in the present moment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
