<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tutorial on 🏠 Home</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tutorial on 🏠 Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 20:29:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Make a Local Email Spam Filter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/make-a-local-email-spam-filter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 20:29:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/make-a-local-email-spam-filter/</guid>
      <description>In this we will be creating a spam filter using a Raspberry Pi to remove all the incoming spam messages.&#xA;This assumes that you already have a fully working Raspberry Pi with any of the Linux distros available with Systemd as an init service. Note:&#xA;This only works for unmonitored clients such as thunderbird and other offline FOSS applications. I have not tried it on online email clients like Gmail and other proprietary spying websites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Torrent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/make-your-own-torrent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 10:13:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/make-your-own-torrent/</guid>
      <description>You are based if you seed torrent.&#xA;&amp;ndash;Probably Someone&#xA;Torrent have a bad image when it comes to downloading thing, like movies, music and most importently ISO&amp;rsquo;s for your Linux distro.&#xA;Well, then lets not waist time and make and make some torrents.&#xA;Pre-requisites Qbittorrent(client) A good/reliable/fast internet connection The file you want to seed Well if you have all the above then follow the steps below.&#xA;If not then Fuck off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lets Join Tilde Varsh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 22:48:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/lets-join-tilde-varsh/</guid>
      <description>Few weeks ago I came across this thing called a tilde on the gnulinuxindia.org website, while lurking around the web. I had zero idea about what it was about or what even is it. So in their terms it is&#xA;An India-based shared unix system which focuses on mutual development of skills and sharing of ideas. Services are secondary in this tilde, community is prime.&#xA;&amp;ndash; Tildevarsh&#xA;Still confused watch this Video</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neovim Customization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/nvim-customization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 08:48:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/nvim-customization/</guid>
      <description>Why use vim and neovim over other text editors and IDEs? For me, I&amp;rsquo;ve always loved minimalism and performance over ease of use and other flashy bloat no one really uses and cares about. This why I personally use Terminal-based text editors. Preferably VIM or Neovim. Tho I currently, am running Neovim, but both of them are basically the same. NeoVIM is a little bit more extensible than VIM and easy to manage imo.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
